forexball.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy - ForexBall

* * *

This privacy policy sets out how Admiral Markets (AM), the organizer of the ForexBall™ contest (FXB) and MTrading (MT), a co-participant in FXB, use and protect any information that you give when you use the FXB website.

Each participant’s privacy is protected. Should you be asked to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then rest assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

This policy may be changed from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree with any changes. The current policy is effective from 01/11/2014.

* * *

##  WHAT DATA IS COLLECTED

Only your personal data which you have knowingly provided is collected, this information may include:  
• Your name  
• Your trading history;  
• Contact information, including email address, phone number and address;  
• Completed interview answers or short story of success;  
• Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.;  
• Scan of ID and photo in real life (not a photo from document);

* * *

##  WHY IS THE INFORMATION GATHERED

The information is required to understand your needs and to provide you with a better service, in particular for the following reasons:  
• Internal record keeping.  
• To improve offered products and services;  
• To send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which you may find interesting, using the email address which you have provided;  
• From time to time, your information may also be used to contact you for marketing purposes, e.g. by email, phone, fax or mail.

* * *

##  SECURITY

Every effort is made to ensure that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been put in place to safeguard and secure the information that is collected online. All of the personal information collected from you on the site, including names, addresses etc. are stored behind a "firewall".

* * *

##  USE OF COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Traffic log cookies are used to identify which pages are being used. This helps to analyze data about web page traffic and improve the FXB website in order to tailor it to customer needs. This information is only used for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help to provide you with a better website, by enabling to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie doesn't give any access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

* * *

##  LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

The FXB website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave the FXB site, you should note that AM or MT may not have any control over that other website. Therefore, AM or MT cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

As you browse [www.forexball.com] and other websites, online ad networks we work with may place anonymous cookies on your computer, and use similar technologies, in order to understand your interests based on your (anonymous) online activities, and thus to tailor more relevant ads to you. If you do not wish to receive such tailored advertising, you can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of most companies that engage in such advertising. (This will not prevent you from seeing ads; the ads simply will not be delivered through these targeting methods.)

* * *

##  CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you have previously agreed to use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing at [info@forexball.com](mailto:info@forexball.com)

Any of your personal information will not be sold, distributed or leased to third parties without your permission, unless disclosure is required by law. AM or MT may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information AM or MT is holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write or email as soon as possible, at [support@admiralmarkets.com](mailto:support@admiralmarkets.com) for Admiral Markets or [support@mtrading.com](mailto:support@mtrading.com) for MTrading. Any information found to be incorrect will be promptly corrected. Requests by postal mail for AM may be sent to:

Admiral Markets  
Ahtri 6A (Admiral House), 5th floor  
Tallinn 10151  
Estonia

MTrading  
Suite 5, Garden City Plaza  
Mountainview Boulevard  
City of Belmopan, Belize
